rizzoma.com 2019-07-05

# Rizzoma privacy policy

## Privacy policy

Last updated: January 18, 2013. 

This Privacy Policy describes Rizzoma’s policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information when you use the Rizzoma service. By accessing or using the Service, you agree to this Privacy Policy. Basic and General terms of the service disclosed on Terms of Use. 

### Content

You also provide us information in Content you post to the Service. Your Content and metadata about your Content may be viewed by other users in accordance with your settings. Unless Content is made viewable in accordance with your settings on the Service, Rizzoma and Rizzoma emloyees will not view your content except as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Information We Collect and Use

Rizzoma uses information we collect to operate, maintain and provide you the features and functionality of the Service, to analyze how the Service is used, diagnose service or technical problems, maintain security, personalize content, remember information to help you efficiently access your account, monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns, and track Content and users as necessary to comply with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act and other applicable laws.

### Personal Information

You provide us information about yourself, such as your name and email address, if you register for an account with the Service, including by connecting with the Service via a third-party service, or by “following,” “becoming a fan,” adding the Rizzoma application, etc., on a third-party website or network. Your name, email address and other information you choose to provide on the Service will be viewable in accordance with your settings on the Service.

We may use your email address to send you Service-related notices. We may also use your contact information to send you marketing messages. If you don’t want to receive these messages, you can opt out by following the instructions in the message. If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address and our responses.

If you choose to use our invitation service to invite a colleague or a friend to the Service, we will ask you for that person’s email address and automatically send an email invitation. Rizzoma stores this information to send this email, to register your friend if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our invitation service.

### Cookies

When you use the Service, we may send one or more “cookies” – a small data file – to your computer to uniquely identify your browser and let Rizzoma help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may convey anonymous information about how you browse the Service to us. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser so that it can be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Service. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

### Log Files

When you use the Service, our servers automatically record certain information sent by your web browser. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Service, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, mobile carrier, and other such information.

### Clear Gifs Information

When you use the Service, we may employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting and make Rizzoma better for our users.

### Third-Party Tools

Rizzoma uses third-party analytics tools, such as Google Analytics, to help understand use of the Service. Many of these tools collect the information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, including cookies and your IP address. These analytics tools also receive this information and their use of it is governed by their privacy policy.

Rizzoma may use a remarketing tag to advertise online. This means that Google and other third-party vendors may show our ads to you on sites across the Internet. These third-party vendors, including Google, may use cookies to serve ads to you based upon your past visits to our website.

We use DoubleClick cookie and remarketing code to log when users view specific pages, allowing us to provide targeting advertising in the future. 

If you would like to opt out of Google’s use of cookies, you can visit the company’s Ad Preferences Manager at <https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/>. In the alternative, you can opt out of the use of cookies by third-party vendors by going to the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page located at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

### Service Providers, Business Partners, and Others

Rizzoma may share your personally identifiable information with other third-parties with your permission and only after you confirmation of the access request. If we do this, such third-parties’ use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Policy. We may also store personal information in locations outside the direct control of Rizzoma (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers).

### Business Transfers

Customers' email, and visitor information is one of the untransferred business assets. Information is strongly connected with Rizzoma service and can't be used separately of Rizzoma service.

### Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests; Protection of Rizzoma's Rights

Rizzoma may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues.

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We may disclose your non-private, aggregated, or otherwise non-personally identifiable information, such as anonymous usage data, platform types, etc., with interested third-parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain Rizzoma Services.
